Rochester, New York and Vicinity Labor Council, AFL-CIO Audio-Visual Materials 6239 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Rochester, New York and Vicinity Labor Council, AFL-CIO Audio-Visual Materials
1986-2004
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Garlock, Jonathan
Anderson, Marilyn
Rochester and Vicinity Labor Council, AFL-CIO
6239 AV
0.5 cubic feet
0.5 linear ft.
Audiovisual materials.
7544183
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, June 07, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 25, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Rochester and Vicinity Labor Council
7544183
- 1988 Labor Day, 1 (Box 1)
- 1989 Labor Day Parade, 2 (Box 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Dub
- 1986 Labor Day Parade, 3 (Box 1)
- Labor Day Parade - 2002 - W/BITC, 4 (Box 1)
- Not labeled, 5 (Box 1)
- 2003 Labor Day Parade - Full Parade, 6 (Box 1)
- 2003 Labor day Parade - Full Parade, 7 (Box 1)
- 2004 Labor Day Parade, 8 (Box 1)
- 2004 Labor Day Parade, 9 (Box 1)
- 2004 Labor Day Parade, 10 (Box 1)
- Struggle in Smugtown - 3/19/2002, 11 (Box 1)